Well.
嗯。
Fresh.
清新。
At the same time, there is an old saying in China this year.
同时狮子今年中国有句古语。
Notify me.
通知我。
Brothers are good people, China International Television, telephone, in, seven, new.
兄弟是好人，中国国际电视，联系电话，在，七，新。
Friends。
朋友们。
Ladies and gentlemen.
女士们，先生们。
2016 is about to pass.
2016年，即将过去。
The new year's bell is about to ring.
新年的钟声，即将敲响。
This is a good day for the new year.
这日子就迎新的，美好时刻。
I to the people of all ethnic groups.
我向全国各族人民。
Compatriots in the Hongkong special administrative region.
向香港特别行政区同胞。
Our special administrative region compatriots.
我们特别行政区同胞。
Taiwan compatriots and overseas chinese.
希望台湾同胞，和海外侨胞。
Friends from all over the world.
向世界各国，各地区的朋友们。
Best wishes for the new year.
新年的祝福。
2016.
2016年。
Well, for the Chinese people, it's Sun Fanli.
嗯，中国人民来说，是孙凡利你。
Well, I forgot.
嗯，老子忘了。
十三五，实现了，开门红。
We actively practice, the new law.
我们积极践行，新法律。
The process of building a well off society in an all round way.
交通全面建成小康社会进程。
China's economic growth, continue to walk in the forefront of the world.
春风我国经济增长，继续，走在世界前列。
We actively promote the comprehensive deepening of reform.
我们积极推进，全面深化改革。
Structural reform of the supply side, an important step.
供给侧结构性改革，迈出重要步伐。
Imitation, the army after the song, made a major breakthrough.
模仿，后军队的歌，取得重大突破。
Roll feeling body frame has four beams eight columns of happiness, has been basically established.
滚具有四梁八柱幸福的感觉主体框架，已经基本确定。
We actively promote the overall rule of law.
我们积极推进，全面依法治国。
Whether or not to mention cousin, to promote, criminal justice, safeguard, social justice.
生活是否提及表哥，全力促进，刑法公正，维护，社会公平正义。
We actively promote the party strictly.
我们积极推进，全面从严治党。
Does not affect others.
并不影，保护他人。
You are?
你是？
Well, political ecology.
嗯，政治生态。
The wind social atmosphere, continue to improve.
党风政风社会风气，继续好转。
2016.
2016年。
China tianyu.
中国天宇。
Chery.
奇瑞。
Tomorrow sun, Zhao Yunhang a year.
明天晒，赵云行一年。
Days fly to space.
日子还飞向太空。
The Shenzhou 11 Tiangong 2, travel star.
神舟11号天宫2号，遨游星汉。
Chinese Olympic athletes Yong success.
中国奥运健儿勇创佳绩。
Chinese women's volleyball team after a lapse of twelve years, once again boarded the Olympic Games, the highest podium.
中国女排时隔十二年，再次登上奥运会，最高领奖台。
Also。
还有。
Second elder brother。
二哥。
The transfer of rural population, more convenient.
农村转移人口市民化，更便利了。
Many children in poor areas, school conditions, improved.
许多贫困地区孩子们，上学条件，改善了。
So and so on the credibility and identity cards, friends playing red light fire.
某某信誉并办理身份证，朋友玩红灯火了。
Are you a long time no account?
你是长期无户口的人？
According to account.
根据户口。
Many people have their own children, family doctors.
很多群众有了自己的儿，家庭医生。
Each river, there is a photo.
每条河流，要有合照了。
Really, let's be thankful.
真是，让我们，感到欣慰。
2015.
2015年。
West lake.
专门的西子湖畔。
Not allowed to report to the leadership of the group of twenty, the Eleventh summit.
不许报了二十国集团领导，第十一次峰会。
The contribution of Chinese wisdom to the world, China wind, and also to show the world a magnificent, China impression, China style.
向世界贡献了中国智慧，中国风啊，也向世界展示了，美轮美奂的，中国印象，中国风采。
A screen to make rapid progress.
一道银幕建树快速推进。
Medium infrastructure investment bank, officially opened.
中期础设施投资银行，正式开张。
We adhere to peaceful development.
我们，坚持和平发展。
Music number, territorial sovereignty, good crowd.
音乐号为，领土主权，好好人群。
Who is going to roll in this ghost place, the Chinese people, never promise.
谁要在这个鬼地方滚装，中国人民，绝不答应。
As for women.
至于女人。
Why in the world, my safety accident?
为什么自然界上，我安全事故？
Well, life and property, and production and life, causing serious losses.
嗯，生命财产，和生产生活，造成严重损失。
We deeply regret.
我们深感痛惜。
China, several comrades peacekeepers, heroic sacrifice.
中国，维和部队的几名同志，壮烈牺牲。
World peace has given its precious life.
世界和平献出了宝贵生命。
We miss them.
我们怀念他们。
Embrace their loved ones.
拥抱他们的亲人，中。
20160? Do we want to go to Chongqing? The 95 anniversary of the founding of the Communist Party of china.
20160？我们隆重庆祝吗？中国共产党成立，95周年。
To commemorate the eighty anniversary of the victory of the Chinese Communist Party and the red army.
纪念某中国工农红军，长征胜利，八十周年。
Bright moon floor, well, the Chinese people, and the Chinese nation, the government contributed to the predecessors.
明月楼距，嗯，中国人民，和中华民族，政府贡献的前辈们。
Hearts, move on.
红心，继续前进。
Comrades, friends, ladies and gentlemen.
同志们，朋友们，女士们，先生们。
New home spring, rising not to.
新故乡春，日升不至。
The coming 2017.
即将到来的2017年。
The Communist Party of China will hold the nineteenth national congress.
中国共产党，将召开第十九次，全国代表大会。
全面建成小康社会，全面深化改革。
Forestry rule of law, strict party strictly, to continue to force.
林业依法治国，全面从严治党，要继续发力。
The sun never pie.
孙总不会掉馅儿饼。
Work hard to make your dreams come true.
努力奋斗，才能梦想成真。
A bear on the road, can not be left behind.
熊横路上一座，都不能掉队。
You Meng niu.
你牛氓。
About 10000000 poor people, to achieve poverty.
1000多万贫困人口，实现了脱贫。
Dressed in poverty alleviation frontline comrades hard, I pay tribute to comrades.
盛装着脱贫攻坚一线的同志们辛苦了，我向同志们致敬。
On the occasion of the new year.
新年之际。
Should be, or difficult masses.
应该的，还是困难群众。
What medicine did they take? No noon.
他们吃过什么药？中午不行哟。
We have a good new year, the Spring Festival in Guangzhou.
我们过好新年，广州春节。
Oolong drama.
乌龙剧。
Love.
爱。
My day, children education.
我日，子女教育。
Well, housing and so on, but also face some difficulties.
嗯，住房等方面，还面临一些困难。
It is the bounden duty of the party and the government to solve these problems.
不断解决好这些问题，是党和政府，义不容辞的责任。
The whole Party and the whole society should continue to care for and help the poor and the needy.
全党全社会要继续关心和帮助，贫困人口，和有困难的群众。
龙哥跟嫂子承诺，惠及更多群众，让人民生活更加幸福美满。
In unison　 wins.
上下同欲者胜。
If more than 1 billion 300 million people work together with one heart.
只要13亿多，人民和衷共济。
Let me not understand, always stand together with the people.
让我不懂，永远同人民站在一起。
Dragon 75 yong.
龙75家勇哥。
We can certainly, who? Originally a meal, Changchun road.
我们就，一定能过，谁？原本是一顿咯，长春路。
Comrades, friends, ladies and gentlemen.
同志们，朋友们，女士们，先生们。
Chinese people have always advocated that the world.
中国人历来主张，世界大同天下一教。
The Chinese people not only want to have a good life, but also hope that the people of all countries.
中国人民不仅希望自己过得好，也希望各国人民过了。
Short skirt。
短裙。
And comments, parenting plagued some countries and regions.
而且评论，育儿困扰着部分国家和地区。
Disease and disaster, many people are sometimes Qing Zhuo?
疾病和灾难，有时是清溪濯众多的人吗？
I sincerely hope that the international community to join hands, ten, the concept of human destiny community.
我真诚希望，国际社会携起手来，十，人类命运共同体的理念。
A hundred years of ignorance, the song, more peace, more prosperity.
百年不知心球，这首歌，更加和平，更加繁荣。
Let us full of confidence and expectation.
让我们满怀信心和期待。
The new year bell.
爱情认知，新年的钟声。
Resulting reef.
致使岛礁。